<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, StrobeActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Strobily</string>
    <string name="S_AD">xfes5</string>
    <string name="S_WIDGET">widget</string>
    
    <string name="free_link">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tp77.StrobeAd</string>
    <string name="paid_link">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tp77.Strobe</string>
    
    <string name="troubleshoot">If the strobe light isn\'t working for you, try these settings. DROID phones will almost definitely need the preview hack. The gentle
        strobe is new and is for phones whose drivers can be easily overwhelmed by LED commands.
       	\n\nIn any case, if you are having trouble, I still love getting these emails. (The email is already 
        filled out for you.)</string>
        
        
    <string name="calculations_text">1. Enable airplane mode outside this app\n2.
        Enable airplane mode inside this app with the checkbox\n3.
        Long-click \"Save ON Length\" for 0 ms ON length\n4.
        Check \"Steady ON length\"\n5.
        Get frequency close with sliders\n6.
        Press \"Hide\" button\n7.
        Fine tune frequency with volume keys\n8.
        Adjust the settings above\n9.
        Lock phone and wait for system to settle</string>
        
    <string name="beta_testing">This summer I\'m going to be completely rewriting this app with all the new skillz I\'ve picked up.
        But with any complete rewrite, it\'s important to test it out before giving it to the general public to avoid one-stars.
        I need some people who enjoy this app to become my beta testers and try out the new version.
        \nPros:
        \n - The new version will be <b>awesome</b>
        \n - You\'ll get to see it a few months early
        \nCons:
        \n - It might not work right
        \n\nSo if you\'re interested, click the link below. You always have the choice to leave the beta if you get annoyed.</string>
        
    <string name="new_version_text">- Fixed issue with hand-typing hz
        \n- Fixed a bunch more crashes
        \n\n- Is the app crash-proof now? Almost...
        </string>
        
    <string name="music_battery">This uses <i><b>a lot</b></i> of power. Connect your charger if you are going to use this for more than 10 minutes.</string>
        
    <string name="turntable_text">Welcome to the Strobily turntable calibrator. This is for calibrating your record-playing
        turntables. To begin, you\'ll need to attach a pattern to your turntable. A good start would be to search \"strobe calibrate 
        turntable\" on Google.</string>
        
    <string name="turntable_text2">Select the highest frequency that is green, then adjust your turntable until the pattern appears 
        to stop moving.</string>
        
    <string name="widget_text">Welcome to the Strobily widget creator. This page allows you to set any of your saved <b>patterns</b>
        as widgets that you can click on your homescreen.
        \n\nTo begin, select a pattern:
    </string>
    
    <string name="tacho_help_1">This part of the app uses sound to identify the frequency of a spinning object. To use it, find a spinning
        object that is making a sound and press one of the four buttons to take a sound sample.
        \n\nWhen the results appear, the first number is the frequency that was identified and the other buttons represent fractions of that frequency.
        The greener a button is, the stronger that frequency was identified. (However if they\'re all green, most likely no match was found.) Normal-colored
        buttons did not rank in the top 5.
        \n\nIf your spinning object is not making a sound, you may have to intervene. An example would be sticking a playing card into a fan in order
        to make a repeating sound.
        </string>
        
    <string name="email_body">
        \n
        \nDid your LED work in the beginning? :
        \nAutofocus hack result:
        \nPreview hack result:
        \n
        \n(I read all of these by hand, so feel free to write whatever you want)
        \nStrobily v%1$s (%2$d)
        \nDevice type: %3$s
        \nDevice Firmware: %4$s
        </string>
        
    
    <string name="email_body2">
        \n
        \n
        \n
        \nStrobily v%1$s (%2$d)
        \nDevice type: %3$s
        \nDevice Firmware: %4$s
        </string>
        
    <string name="email_body_friendly">
        \n
        \n
        \n(Make sure you add a subject, I don\'t want an inbox full of (No Subject))
        \nStrobily v%1$s (%2$d)
        \nDevice type: %3$s
        \nDevice Firmware: %4$s
        </string>
    
    <string name="legend_first">
        This graph show what the app was doing during the past 100 flashes. The x-axis width is set so that it exactly
        matches the frequency of the strobe. \n\n
        If the graph is this color, the app is:
    </string>
  
</resources>
